

Maria Montagu

Web designer - UI/UX oriented

Career goals

I am a web designer with a passion for user interfaces, user experience, web design, frontend programming and recently design systems.

I am a passionate and creative person who loves to learn new things and collaborate with teams to create great user experiences.



Contact

- +33 6 31 30 76 30
- mariafmontagu@gmail.com
- in linkedin.com/in/mariafmontagu/
- https://mafemont16.github.io/portfolio/
- ♥ Marseille, France

Technical skills

Technologies

HTML, CSS, Material UI, React.js, JavaScript, TypeScript.

Content management systems

WordPress

Project management tools

Git, GitHub, Jira, Bitbucket

Tools

Figma Notion

Microsoft Office

Visual Studio Code

Languages

Spanish : native French : intermediate

English: fluent

Hobbies

Running Reading

Education

2020 - 2021 Full-stack web development training

ÉCOLE CENTRALE DE MARSEILLE

PASSERELLE NUMÉRIQUE

9 months training in full-stack web development (front-end and back-end web development, databases, algorithms, agile

methods, CMS).

www.passerelle-numerique.fr

2015 - 2016 Master Marketing & Brand Management

KEDGE BUSINESS SCHOOL - MARSEILLE

Qualitative & Quantitative Research, Strategic Brand Management, Experiential branding & consumption, Sustainable Marketing, Marketing Decision-Making, BtoB Marketing, Services Marketing

2006 - 2010 **B.sc. Economics**

UNIV. PONTIFICIA BOLIVARIANA - COLOMBIA

Professional experience

Front-end Developer

SUBCLIC - MARSEILLE | JULY 2021 - SEPT. 2022

Develop and redesign of the Back-office's front-end using React.js,
TypeScript, Material UI, GraphQL, Webpack

Front-end Developer - 6 week internship

OWARD | MAR. 2021 - APR. 2021

 Developed and redesigned the subscription page and navigation bar using React.js / TypeScript / SASS / Bulma

Customer Success Associate

TRAXENS | SEPT. 2019 - MAR. 2020

 Assisted CMA-CGM and MSC customers in the use of Traxens IoT solution in their containers

Marketing Project Manager

NCC PARTNERS | AUG. 2018 - JULY 2019

 Organized and promoted the International Mobile Gaming Awards event in San Francisco, aimed at gaming companies and game developers

Marketing Manager

DÉCOUVERTES | JAN. 2017 - JULY 2018

• Implemented marketing strategies and HubSpot CRM

Marketing Analyst - Internship

THALES | MAR. 2016 - OCT. 2016

 Monitored analytics and key programs for Gemalto's LinqUs Personal Cloud services